(Sheldon:)...by making a gesture that says,
"Get a load of this guy."
(Leonard:)Fine, Howard, what do you do?
(Howard:)I follow the ogre tracks,
checking for secret doors along the way.
(Leonard:)And you discover a secret door
leading to a dark corridor.
Let's make a plan. Spellcasters in the back,
warriors in the front.
(Raj:)Screw that noise, I'm going in.
Hang on, Santa, I'm coming for you.
(Leonard:)Okay. You run into a room full of weapons,
hit a trip wire.
(Leonard:)A cannon blows your face off.
You die, you're out of the game.
What? A cannon?
(Raj:)Am I really out of the game?
(Sheldon:)Lucky.
(Leonard:)Okay, come on. Moving on.
(Raj:)Wait, doesn't anyone have
a rod of resurrection?
(Raj:)Because if you've got one, I need it bad.
(Raj:)Get in here with your rod
and give it to me.
(Stuart:)Okay, you need to say these things
in your head before you say them out loud.